[Music]
[Música]
Good night Are you okay how are you The
Buenas noches Estás bien cómo estás lo
first thing is that I don't know How long
primero es que no sé Hace cuánto ha
this has been going on or anything uh I'm very
pasado esto ni nada eh estoy muy
angry indignant upset depressed disgusted
enfadada
everything everything everything that ends
asqueada todo todo todo lo que termine
nothing like this this me with him look I'm going to
nada así esto yo con él mira yo voy a
put it in stop and I think it's the first
poner en para y creo que es la primera
time FJ that I've spoken to someone I've
vez FJ que yo hablo con alguien no lo he
never put it I've been with this story for 2 years
puesto nunca llevo 2 años con esta
and and it's over my daughter is Yes
historia y y ya se acabó mi hija es Sí
my daughter is a lawyer and when she comes back from
mi hija es abogada y cuando venga de
Switzerland we will possibly take measures uh I
Suiza tomaremos medidas posiblemente eh
met Antonio many years ago
yo conocí a Antonio hace muchos años
working with him you helped in something well I
trabajando con él ayudabas en algo bueno
don't want to get into what I don't
no quiero entrar tampoco en lo que no sí
work we worked at the
trabaj trabajábamos en el restaurante
nautical restaurant in Almerimar okay But if you can
náutico de almerimar vale Pero si puedes
save some Cos not public I mean I
ahorrar algunos Cos no se públicas o sea
mean everything that is private so as not to
es decir todo lo que sea privado para no
have any type of data I go I'm going to do
tener ningún tipo de dat yo voy yo voy a
everything that could be
ahar todo lo que pueda llegar a ser
sued You know that in this I am a
demandable Sabes que en esto estoy un
little bit informed Well with the
poquito puesta ya Bueno pues con
circumstances of life well I
circunstancias de la vida pues lo
found it on YouTube I entered his channel
encontré en YouTube yo entr en su canal
one day Oh Antonio well what joy
un día Ay Antonio pues qué alegría
after many years without  see each other and such
después de muchos años sin vernos y tal
when the story of Loli happened I
cuando pasó la historia de Loli yo me
positioned myself with Javi okay obviously
posicion con Javi vale
obviously there is no other
obviamente obviamente es que no hay otra
option there is no other way it can't
opción que no hay de otro modo es que no
be any other way I mean you have to
puede ser de otra manera O sea tienes
be really bad with me for it
que estar muy fatal conmigo para para
not to be like that you have to have something
que no sea así tienes que tener algo
strange with me for it not to be like that because
conmigo raro para que no sea así porque
First of all I am a person I think I have
Ante todo soy persona creo que tengo
knowledge and I am free Exactly in
conocimientos y soy libre Exacto en
all things yes eh he met me
todas cosas sí eh él me conoció a mí
when I was 29 years old I come from a
cuando yo tenía 29 años Yo vengo de una
relationship of having been an
relación de haber sido una Mujer
abused woman I separated from my husband with
maltratada yo me separé de mi marido con
a restraining order my
una orden de alejamiento conocía mi
current partner knew with whom I have been for 25 years and
actual pareja con la que llevo 25 años y
he dedicated himself to telling a channel that I was
é se dedicó a contar un canal que yo le
cheating on my ex-husband with the one who
ponía los cuernos a mi exmarido con el
is now my husband and this because of
que ahora es mi marido y esto a causa de
positioning yourself of saying that you are with Javi
posicionarte de decir que estás con Javi
basically of course Hello hello have you
bsicamente por supuesto Hola hola habéis
heard the story I mean I
escuchado la historia O sea que me la he
put it here to see what the hell
puesto aquí para ver qué [__] era de
chill was Hello and he justifying that because you
chill Hola y é justificando que porque
knew each other previously outside of
os conocíais previamente fuera de
YouTube and then I met on YouTube he says
YouTube y luego coincidí dice en YouTube
he considers that maybe that must
él considera que a lo mejor eso debe de
be  a betrayal enough to
ser una traición lo suficiente como para
justify the fact of telling things
justificar el hecho de contar cosas
about your life [ __ ] him when they
sobre tu vida hostias él cuando se
started to but this guy wasn't the one who
pusieron al pero este tío no fue el que
well the one who Lio to defend the
bueno el que se Lio a a defender lo
private on other occasions also what
privado en otras ocasiones también qué
is it that he starts to defend
es lo que era que se pone a defender
the private also since
también lo privado ya que le sacábamos
we took him out in the car what happened to Loli's sister
nosotros en carro lo de la hermana de la
My God man some twitterers
Loli Dios mío tío unas tuiteras
exposed photos of him exposed uh
expusieron fotos de él expusieron eh
things about him that I imagine they would have
cosas de él que yo me imagino que la
removed from Google I don't know FJ because cl
sacarían de Google No lo sé FJ porque cl
he lights the flame and and the twitterers and
él enciende la llama y y las twittera y
other people like more of I don't know that they
otra gente como más de no sé que se
cover their
cubren la
backs The live was something
espalda de El directo era algo
referring to adultery okay like there were
refiriéndose a adulterio vale como había
a lot of people who knew that I knew him I
mucha gente que sabía que yo lo conocía
started to receive a lot of
empecé a recibir una cantidad de
edes Raquel you have put Raquel look what
edes Raquel te has puesto Raquel mira lo
Rael says I saw the live obviously he
que habla rael vi el directo obviamente
was talking about me I can't imagine how You
hablaba de mí no me imagino comoo Te
must feel at that moment when
tendrías que sentir en ese momento en el
you receive all those messages and you would
que te llegan todos esos mensajes y te
get nervous and when you go to
pondrías de los nervios y cuando vas a
check what they are telling you you
comprobar lo que te están diciendo te
realize that it is true that it is like that or is it
das cuenta que es verdad que es así o es
even worse  what they were telling you
aún peor de lo que te estaban contando
FJ I am a married working woman I have
FJ soy mujer casada trabajadora tengo
two
dos hijos
spectacular children I have a husband who is sick
espectaculares tengo un marido enfermito
with cancer I expel my husband I expel him
de cáncer expulso a mi marido lo expulso
because he was his boss all out of pure hatred for
porque fue su jefe todo por puro odio a
you but I mean when this happened I did
ti que pero o sea cuando esto pasó que
n't know I mean when this happened I
esto no lo sabía o sea cuando esto pasó
understand that there were people in that chat
entiendo que había gente en ese chat
no when this happened I understand that there were
no cuando esto pasó entiendo que había
people in that chat and
gente en ese chat y tenéis que daros
you have to realize one very serious thing that those people who were in that chat while gard de Troya was doing this were okay with what they were listening to simply to support me I mean out of pure hatred for me they justify it in anything eh Out of
lo justifica en cualquier cosa eh Por
pure hatred for me eh they are defending er
puro odio a mí eh están defendiendo er
the ra is joining whoever whatever
al ra está uniéndose a quien sea lo que
comes out
salga
okay if something happened to me
vale si a mí me pasara algo el día de
tomorrow they would defend him those people would
mañana lo defenderían esa gente lo
defend him my god I've really been
defenderían madre mía de verdad llevo
silent for two years I've had the opportunity
dos años callada he tenido oportunidad
to enter Javi I've had the opportunity
de entrar d Javi he tenido oportunidad
to enter the flight I've had the
de entrar en el vuelo he tenido
opportunity to enter many places
oportunidad de entrar en muchos sitios
to defend myself how heavy eh because
para defenderme qué heavy eh porque
nobody has to think that I'm neither a
nadie tiene por pensar que yo soy ni una
[ __ ] nor an alcoholic that was it  The last thing he
[__] ni un alcohólica que fue lo último
said about me is an alcoholic, I work at
que dijo de m una alcohólica trabajo en
a 24/7 store, my daughter is a
una me ti 24 siete trabajando mi hija es
lawyer, my son is my son is a charmer,
abogada mi hijo es mi hijo es un Encanto
my son is a very hard-working child, independent,
mi hijo es un niño muy trabajador indep
what a pain, kid. What people are we
qué heavy chaval Con qué gente estamos
arguing with? eh, they expose me on channels
discutiendo eh se me exponen en canales
when I am an anonymous person,
cuando yo soy una persona anónima
anonymous FJ, I don't expose myself,
anónima FJ yo no me expongo yo no he
I haven't said anything about him, I haven't spoken about
soltado de él nada yo no he hablado de
him at all, and even Cerda has called me
él para nada y me ha llamado hasta Cerda
because he thinks that everything you know
porque se piensa que todo lo que saben
on Twitter was me who said it,
en Twitter he sido yo quien lo ha dicho
and no, it's not true because I don't have time, I do
y no No es cierto porque no tengo tiempo
n't have much work, but it gives me. What's wrong with
no lo tengo trabajo mucho pero me da Qué
Pablo? I wake up with what he says
pasa Pablo que despierto cu lo que diga
about me, the last thing he said on one of his
de mí lo último que dijo en uno de su
live shows? Yes, yes, that her husband is
directo Sí sí una que su marido está
sick like Prince Charles,
malito como el príncipe Carlos
referring to Paco, who had
refiriéndose a Paco que tenido un cáncer
stomach cancer, they removed his
de estómago que le han quitado el
stomach, and he spent three months in the ICU
estómago y estuvo tres meses en la UCI
intubated and sedated. Ugh, and I've been
entubado y sedado Uf y yo llevo do años
living a [ __ ] martyrdom for two years. And this isn't
viviendo un [__] martirio Y esto no es
fair, and after the other day when he
justo y después del otro día que me
called me an alcoholic, man, seriously, seriously,
llamó alcohólica tío en serio en serio
who are we dealing with, right?
con quién estamos tratando eh verdad
But we're crazy FJ, but we're with
pero estamos loco FJ pero estamos con
who we are treating eh nothing bad to
quiénes estamos tratando eh nada malo a
anyone that I to everyone with affection
nadie que yo a todo el mundo con cariño
that I enter Twitter that I follow two
que yo entro a Twitter que yo sigo dos
channels that are yours and Javi's and
canales que es el tuyo y el de Javi y
what are you saying that
qué es lo que estáis diciendo que ha
he said today or rather you are saying out
dicho él hoy o sea estáis diciendo por
there today on his channel he put them fine
ahí hoy en su canal los ha puesto fino
for the call victimizing himself for the
por la llamada victimizandose por la
death of his father he is an unpresentable
muerte de su padre es un impresentable
Ah he used that and I the truth eh I
Ah ha utilizado eso e yo la verdad eh
think you are not going to let me lie
creo que no me vais a dejar mentir
you know that in these last days
sabéis que en estos últimos días No
We have not made content of de ard de Troya
hemos hecho contenido de de ard de Troya
Because someone told me by WhatsApp that
Porque alguien me avisó por WhatsApp que
the father had died or that he had
se había muerto el padre o que había
done I don't know if he had posted a tweet or had done
hecho no sé si había puesto un tweet o
a live saying that
había hecho un directo diciendo que se
the father had died And then I told him
había muerto el padre Y entonces le dije
not only did we not do a live but I
no solamente no hicimos directo sino que
also told Lili don't upload any
además le dije a Lili no subas ningún
excerpts stop it pause the excerpts that
extracto páralo pausa los extractos que
are left over from Troya that
tenga sobrar de Troya que se ha muerto
the father has died leave him these days no
el padre déjale estos días no
eh that they are not people who deserve it
eh que no son gente que se la merezcan
Because if if it were me if it were me they would
Porque si si fuera yo si fuera a mí a mí
even be taking out a video with
me estarían sacando hasta un vídeo con
a headline of sad Goodbye from the  mother
un titular de triste Adios de la madre
of Javi Oliveira do you understand me But the
de de Javi oliveira me entiendes Pero la
thing is that your
la cuestión es que que se haya muerto tu
father dying doesn't take this away this happened
padre no quita esto esto ha pasado antes
before your father died and this is being
de que se muera tu padre y esto lo está
told by a person without knowing what
contando una persona sin saber lo que
you have or don't have or I don't know what I mean you know it's what it's
tienes o no tienes o no sé qué O sea que
always the same dude they are
sabes es lo es lo de siempre tío son
different people than
personas diferentes a las personas
normal people Javi There are so many things that you do
normales Javi Hay tantas cosas de las
n't know what I tell you I mean
que no eres conocedor qué te digo O sea
obviously I don't follow anyone else
evidentemente que no sigo a nadie más
that's where I have a good time I don't understand
que es donde me lo paso bien no te claro
I mean how am I going to know these things
Yo es que estas cosas como las voy a
I can't know it would be impossible it's that you guys you guys
saber yo no puedo saber sería imposible
think that I have to
es que ustedes ustedes os creéis que yo
know everything about each follower
tengo que saber todo lo de cada seguidor
that fights with another with I don't know what
que se pelea con otro con no sé qué
many times it's like dude do you realize
muchas veces es como tío os dais cuenta
that for example one day one day chill
que por ejemplo un día un día chill
we are 15 people You know what 15
somos 15 personas Tú sabes lo que son 15
people are well 10000 here in the live
personas bueno 10000 aquí en el directo
that then maybe the next day I'll
que luego a lo mejor al día siguiente la
come to you plus 20,000 I mean do you think that I
vengo otas 20,000 O sea crees que yo
know the 20,000 people that
conozco a las 20,000 personas que me
follow me or or or or the  100,000 people
siguen o o o o las 100.000 personas que
watching a video on the main channel I don't
ven un vídeo en el canal principal no
know the 100,000 people I don't know if
conozco a las 100,000 personas no sé si
one gets along with the other I don't know if a
una se lleva mal con otra No sé si un
youtuber messes with a person on
youtuber se mete con una persona de
Twitter who also follows me, I mean these
Twitter que además me sigue a mí o sea
are things that don't make sense You think
son cosas que no tiene sentido Tú crees
the loser loves someone is that we
que el pringado quiere a alguien es que
are talking to people who
estamos hablando ante personas que
function in a different way in
funcionan de una manera diferente ante
the world, in families, in
el mundo ante las familias ante la
society where I have a serious time, I mean it's that
sociedad dónde me lo pas en serio o sea
Just like he attacks
es que Igual igual que ataca de esta
a person in this way because he
forma vale a una persona porque
considers that he is on the opposite side
considera que está en el bando contrario
and he doesn't care about taking a private message from an
y no le importa sacar privado de una
anonymous person, okay, so that's the
persona anónima vale o sea que el el el
idiot this one of the tro was Oy
mamarracho este de las de tro estaba Oy
Dallas has been criticized for insulting
el Dallas le han criticado por insultar
Father Miari for posting his photo which is
al padre miari por poner su foto que es
an anonymous person and then what he
una persona anónima y luego él lo que ha
did with a girl thinking it was
hecho con una chavala pensándose que era
Lily and then now what he is saying
Lily y luego ahora lo que está contando
this you know, I mean these are people are
esta sabes o sea son personas son
people who act like this are people who that
personas que actúan así son personas que
have this behavior Look
que que tienen este proceder son Mira
just like you are seeing how he is
igual que tú lo estás viendo como está
attacking this person because he
arremetiendo contra esta persona porque
considers her that  right now he's on the
la considera que ahora mismo está en el
other side okay eh Because because
otro lado vale eh Porque porque me sigue
the person follows me no well it's the same as he's
a mí la persona no pues igual que está
turned against her yeah maybe tomorrow
remetido contra ella sí lo mismo mañana
a Tania grabs you and she and
a una Tania te la coge y te la y y te
defends Tania's husband
defiende al marido de la Tania
telling you that the sentence well that
diciéndote que la sentencia bueno que
all the judges who dealt with that
que todos los jueces que trataron ese
case were wrong those of the first
caso se equivocaron los de la primera
instance those of the second all all
instancia los de la segunda todos todos
all the one who knows everything is him you don't
todos el que sabe todo es él no los
know that maybe in that he gets into an argument
sabes que lo mismo en eso le pilla pelea
with Tania and even catches and catches Tania
con Tania y pilla hasta y pilla la Tania
more than her husband you know I mean they're people they're
más que el marido sabes o sea son gente
rabble they're rabble we are we
son chumm son chusmas estamos nosotros
are on one side And on the other side
estamos en un bando Y en el otro lado
have you have people seriously I have to arrive
has hasa gente en serio tengo que lleg
one day to my house sit down at
un día a mi casa sentarme a la hora de
dinner time that I read them at night and
la cena que lleo las dí en la noche y
see md everywhere Raquel has
ver md por todos lados Raquel te ha
put you to put Raquel look what she
puesto a poner ra Raquel mira lo que ha
said is that the last one she didn't even want to
dicho es que el último no quería ni
see him eh I haven't wanted to even see him because I
verlo eh No he querido ni verlo porque
'm not in the best moment of my life
no estoy en el mejor momento de mi vida
right now because right
ahora mismo porque me está saliendo
now you're coming out strong
ahora mismo qué fuerte tú
and suddenly eh after saying that  we
y de repente eh después de decir que nos
knew each other it's true and we knew each other
conocíamos es verdad y nos conocíamos
we got along very well and we went out partying I
llegábamos muy bien y salíamos de marcha
repeat I was 29 years old in the first
repito tenía 29 años en el primer
live I have been a bad mother I have been an
directo Yo he sido mala madre Yo he sido
adulteress I uh a lot of adjectives no longer
adúltera yo eh un montón de adjetivos ya
even derogatory qualifiers I have not
ni calificativos descalificativos Yo no
seen that live I have not wanted to even get involved I am
he visto ese directo no he querido ni
not interested you have them you
meterme no me interesa los tienes los
have them saved you have them downloaded one has downloaded
tienes guardados los tienes descargado
the person who
lo tiene descargado una la persona que
was the one who told me don't worry I
fue la que me dijo No te preocupes que
have the clip here the last one I got
yo tengo el clip aquí el último llego a
home I started looking at Twitter again
mi casa empiez a ver el Twitter otra vez
put rael marinda and I was saying to
puesto rael marinda y decía yo en serio
myself seriously dude that's what I've done now but if I
tío es lo que he hecho yo ahora pero si
don't get into Javi or PJ and the other day
no me meto en Javi ni PJ y el otro día
on the flight I had the great
en el vuelo se me ocurrió la grandiosa
idea when I was with the joke about the car
idea cuando estaba con la coña del coche
to say that but I'm also going to tell you I'm
de decir que pero también te voy a decir
really sorry about his father I'm so
siento muchísimo lo de su padre lo
sorry from the bottom of my
siento en el
heart sincerely zero empathy because the
alma sinceramente empatía cero porque el
day he did the live thing That's why I say that
día que él hizo el directo cosa Por eso
we have to set an
digo que nosotros tenemos que dar
example I mean it's not out of commitment to
ejemplo es decir no es por compromiso
look good it's because we are people
por quedar bien es porque somos personas
and when and when there are certain people who
y cuando y cuando hay ciertas personas
completely lose that empathy
que que pierden por completo esa empatía
that sensitivity  and they wish
esa sensibilidad y le desean cualquier
horrible things on other people Well,
cosa horrible a otras personas Pues
even if that person is the worst, we're
nosotros aunque esa persona sea lo peor
going to be
vamos a ser
people, it has nothing to
personas no tiene su no tiene nada que
do with it, but I'm going to make a small note,
ver pero voy a hacer un pequeño apunte
the day he did the live show, I had just
el día que me hizo el directo acababa de
picked up my husband from the hospital, eh,
recoger a mi marido del hospital eh
after a very difficult operation,
después de una operación muy jodida
I repeat, he has no stomach for it, I spent TR
reitero no tiene estómago me tiré TR
months, they took me five times to
meses que me llevaron cinco veces para
tell me that I was dying, it wasn't the best
decirme que me moría no era el mejor
time to do a live show and I dedicate it to, I
momento de hacerme un directo y dedico a
understand that he wouldn't know, but it's
entiendo que él no lo sabría pero es que
just that it doesn't make sense.
igualmente es que no tiene sentido
None of the live shows knew it. Oh
Ninguno de los directos lo sabía Ah que
yes, I knew it. Oh yes, I knew it. The last thing
sí lo sabía Ah que sí lo sabía lo último
her husband said was someone who is sick
que dijo su marido s uno que está malito
like Prince Charles of England, he is, he is, he is, they are
como el príncipe Carlos de Inglaterra es
bad, they are bad people and
es Es es mala son gente mala